{
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe31",
      "correctAnswer": "Franc",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Peso", "Dollar", "Gira"],
      "question": "What is the basic unit of currency for Equatorial Guinea?",
      "tags": ["currency", "general_knowledge"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ec6",
      "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Oscar Wilde", "Umberto Eco", "Søren Kierkegaard"],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The Elephant Vanishes'?",
      "tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbd8",
      "correctAnswer": "\"You motorboatin’ son of a b****!\"",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "\"I could do this all day\"",
        "\"I’m the guy who does his job. You must be the other guy.\"",
        "\"I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse.\""
      ],
      "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Wedding Crashers'?",
      "tags": ["quotes", "film", "film_and_tv"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "id": "623735d1cfe13103f55eb570",
      "correctAnswer": "Sierra Leone",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Slovenia", "Slovakia", "Sri Lanka"],
      "question": "Which region of the world uses '.sl' at the end of its web addresses?",
      "tags": ["geography"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951605",
      "correctAnswer": "Tomato ",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Onion", "Garlic", "Mango"],
      "question": "'love apple' is a nickname for which food?",
      "tags": ["food_and_drink"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Music",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c3a",
      "correctAnswer": "Coldplay",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Level 42", "Deep Purple", "Feeder"],
      "question": "Which British band released the studio album 'A Head Full of Dreams'?",
      "tags": ["music"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9505ad",
      "correctAnswer": "Medicating patients during surgery",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["Algae", "Karyotypes", "Spiders"],
      "question": "What is Anesthesiology the study of?",
      "tags": ["science", "words"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Film & TV",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501ee",
      "correctAnswer": "David Yates",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Steven Spielberg",
        "Woody Allen",
        "Martin Scorsese"
      ],
      "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows – Part 2?",
      "tags": ["harry_potter", "film", "film_and_tv"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f95181f",
      "correctAnswer": "Abraham Lincoln",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "John F. Kennedy",
        "James Garfield",
        "William McKinley"
      ],
      "question": "Which American president was assassinated in a theatre?",
      "tags": ["presidents", "usa", "assassinations", "events", "history"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9c9",
      "correctAnswer": "Ronald Reagan",
      "incorrectAnswers": ["John Quincy Adams", "Gerald Ford", "James Polk"],
      "question": "Who was the 40th president of the USA, in term during the period 1981–1989?",
      "tags": ["usa", "presidents", "leaders", "history"],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": []
    }
  ],
  "categories": [
    {
      "id": 9,
      "name": "General Knowledge"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "name": "Entertainment: Books"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "name": "Entertainment: Film"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "name": "Entertainment: Music"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "name": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "name": "Entertainment: Television"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "name": "Entertainment: Video Games"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "name": "Entertainment: Board Games"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "name": "Science & Nature"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "name": "Science: Computers"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "name": "Science: Mathematics"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "name": "Mythology"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "name": "Sports"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "name": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "name": "History"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "name": "Politics"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "name": "Art"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "name": "Celebrities"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "name": "Animals"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "name": "Vehicles"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "name": "Entertainment: Comics"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "name": "Science: Gadgets"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "name": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "name": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations"
    }
  ]
}
